http://www.classictube.com/privacy-policy/

Search Make/Model
Year192919311932193319341935193619371938193919401941194219431944194519461947194819491950195119521953195419551956195719581959196019611962196319641965196619671968196919701971197219731974197519761977197819791980198119821983198419851986198719881989199019911992199319941995199619971998199920002001200220032004200520062007200820092010201120122013201420152016 Make Model Ton Duty Drive Cab Box Engine Category
No matches found.
Search
Search Make/Model
Privacy Policy HomePrivacy Policy
Classic Tube Privacy Policy
At Classic Tube, it is very important to us to protect the privacy of your personal information. Whether you are a current client, a returning visitor or just visiting our website for the first time, we are committed to protecting the information you provide to us in the same manner that we protect it when you provide it to us over the phone, in person, or through the mail.
Our policy is simple: we collect personal information about you only when you knowingly and willingly provide it, and we will not share or otherwise profit from the distribution of your personal data beyond the use for which it was provided.
You can visit our website without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. Our web servers collect domain names, not e-mail addresses, of visitors. The personal information we obtain from you is used only to respond to inquiries or to process orders.
Our Web Host provider collects your personal information on behalf of Classic Tube, but in no way can use this information. Your personal information is the sole property of Classic Tube.
We will only disclose your personal information to a third party with your consent or in response to a subpoena or law enforcement request.
SECURITY PRACTICES
Classic Tube, through our Web Host provider, uses a secure server which allows the receipt of online orders and other confidential information in a secure environment. A secure environment refers to the transmission of encrypted information from a web browser to our web server. The user’s web browser encrypts each transaction via our secure online ordering system. Current browser software from Microsoft Explorer and Netscape support this feature. A padlock will appear on the bottom of the web browser to let you know your information is secure.
Only authorized personnel of Classic Tube are able to view these transmissions.
SURVEYS AND FORMS
Classic Tube wants your visit to our website to be informative and enjoyable. We may ask you to voluntarily provide us with information for market research such as your demographics, intended product application, and experience with our products and services. We use this information to better understand your needs and to provide quality products, services and other opportunities. This information will help us improve the content, functionality and overall usefulness of our Website.
Again, we will not share or otherwise profit from the distribution of your personal data.
USE OF INTERNET COOKIES
We may use Internet Cookies on this site to remember the information you provided during a session. The information is to be retained only for that particular session so you don’t have to reenter it as you progress.
UPDATES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY
Evolving technology will continue to provide us with new and better ways to collect, use and protect your personal information. We may revise or update this Privacy Policy in the future to reflect technological advances. We encourage you to return to this page from time to time for any updates.
QUESTIONS ABOUT OUR PRIVACY STATEMENT
If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, please feel free to contact us at anytime.
